

CHOTIRAT JONGGRIT

MSc in Tourism Management

CONTACT DETAILS

Telephone: +32 456 31 68 24 E-mail: jgchotirat@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/chotirat Van Campenhoutstraat 24, 2600 Antwerp, Belgium

LANGUAGE

Thai (Native)
English (Full Professional Proficiency)
Dutch (Limited Working Proficiency)

CORE STRENGTHS

Project management Interpersonal skills Intercultural competence Hospitality management

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Traveling and visiting museums
Reading books
Learning languages (Spanish, French, Danish)
Computer programming (HTML, CSS, &
JavaScript)
Cooking & baking

ABOUT ME

I pride myself on being able to be a fast learner who adapts quickly to change and eager to learn. Lived in 8 different countries, I have learned and gained extensive experience in different cultures and societies. Since 2020, I moved permanently to Antwerp to live with my husband and wish to make Belgium my home.

EDUCATION

Sep 2017 - Sep 2019 European Master in Tourism Management University of Southern Denmark (Denmark), University of Ljubljana (Slovenia), and University of Girona (Spain)

Feb 2013 - Nov 2014 Master's Degree in International Business in Hotel, Resort and Spa Management SWISS HOTEL MANAGEMENT SCHOOL (SWITZERLAND)

May 2008 - Apr 2012 Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration THAMMASAT UNIVERSITY (THAILAND)

Finance (Major) and Real Estates Management (Minor)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2019 - Apr 2020 Member Relations Executive PACIFIC ASIA TRAVEL ASSOCIATION (PATA) (THAILAND)

- Recruited new members and ensured new member engagement
- Managed partnership relationships with existing members
- Developed and updated membership SOP and marketing materials

Nov 2015 - Sep 2016 Assistant Finance Manager Avani sepang goldcoast resort, sepang (malaysia)

Worked on following management projects for the 'Minor Hotel Group'

- Big Data Project: studied the possibility to implement Big Data in the hotel
- The incident management project: examined to resolve guest complaints before their departure
- The re-branding of the hotels

Apr 2015 - Nov 2015 Management Trainee HUVAFEN FUSHI RESORT (MALDIVES)

Worked on the following hotel-based projects:

- Thai dining experience: led a project to improve the guests' experience
- Dry store management: managed and controlled the cost of the dry food store to lower total food costs
- Initiated the planning of the 'Ascent Program' Facebook page to promote Minor hotel group's management training program

May 2014 - Nov 2014 Food And Beverage Trainee COPTHORNE HOTEL LONDON GATWICK (UNITED KINGDOM)

Sep 2012 - Dec 2012 Marketing Communication and CRM officer BUDDY GROUP HOTELS & RESORTS (THAILAND)